Toh Hong Xiang

Self-driven and dependable web developer with 1 year experience, familiar in conducting analysis to pinpoint effective solutions for various end-users. Quick in adapting unfamiliar technologies to deliver impactful products ahead of deadlines. Focused on creating an intuitive, problem-free user experience.

Singapore +65 9431 7592 tohhongxiang@gmail.com

EXPERIENCE

Singapore Armed Forces, Admin Support Assistant

Aug 2019 - Oct 2019

- In charge of designing a small web application to help the management of large complicated menus within SAF Cookhouses
- Implemented website using MongoDB, Express, React and Node
- Focused on clear and intuitive user interfaces to cater to the technologically unfamiliar market
- Significantly lowered error rates by 80%, and increased efficiency by 20%
- <u>Demo</u> and <u>Code</u>

Singapore Armed Forces, Admin Support Assistant

Dec 2018 - Jun 2019

- In charge of leading a small team of developers to help automate resource management using UiPath
- Able to quickly pick up how to use UiPath to deliver a minimum viable product ahead of schedule
- Conducted market analysis to pinpoint major processes that can be improved
- Managed the deployment of the pilot project, and was able to slash man-hours required by 20%

EDUCATION

Anderson Junior College, Singapore

Jan 2017 - Dec 2018

H2 Physics, H2 Math, H2 Chemistry and H1 Economics, with an additional H3 Math. Scored 90 rank points in GCE 'A' Levels 2018

FEATURED PROJECTS

"Stumblr" Social Media Website — Tumblr Clone

- Uses PostgreSQL, Node, Express, React
- Tumblr Clone, features basic CRUD and user authentication
- Demo and Code

Gallereddit — Gallery Visualizer for Reddit

- Uses React and Express
- Data pulled using Reddit and Imgur API
- Features OAuth2 to connect web application to reddit users
- <u>Demo</u> and <u>Code</u>

LINKS

Portfolio https://tohhongxiang123. github.io/Portfolio/

Githubhttps://github.com/tohho
ngxiang123

LinkedIn https://www.linkedin.co m/in/toh-hong-xiang-31 551118b/

SKILLS

Front-End

- HTML, CSS, Javascript
- React
- Vue
- Bootstrap
- SCSS

Back-End

- Node
- Express
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL

Miscellaneous

- Version Control (Git)
- Photoshop/Figma
- Heroku
- Python